A Guide to the Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers FA410
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2010:057 - East 65th Street, 1946-1996; 1; 33.92 Cubic Feet 58 standard document boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 7 record storage boxes
  - Topical Files (East 65th Street), 1942-1996; 2; 22 Cubic Feet
    - Personal Files, 1942-1986; 1
      - Responsibilities by Location and by Employee, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Rippowam Cisqua School Correspondence and "Dare to be True: A History of the Rippowam School: The First 75 Years", 1986-1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Shoe Correspondence, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Tiffany Place Setting, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - University of Maine Honorary Doctor Humane Letters, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - University of Maine Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Westbrook College Honorary Doctor of Letters, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - 15th Wedding Anniversary Party, 1955 September 10 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 20th Wedding Anniversary Party, 1950 September 10 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - 25th and 50th Wedding Anniversary Invitation and Plates, 1965, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - 40th Wedding Anniversary Dinner-Dance, Hudson Pines, 1980 September 6 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 45th Wedding Anniversary Party, 1985 October 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - 48th Wedding Anniversary, 1988 September 7 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 50th Wedding Anniversary Party Sept 8, 1990 and Joan Ganz Cooney and Peter G. Peterson 80th Birthday Party for Peggy Rockefeller's and 50th Wedding Anniversary Party Sept. 28, 1990, 1990 September 8, September 28 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - 50th Wedding Anniversary Party, Hudson Pines, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1990 September 8 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 55th Wedding Anniversary Party Invitation and Original Wedding Plate, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - 80th Birthday "Thank You" Letter from Peggy Rockefeller, 1995 (Box 33, Folder data_value_missing_43a7471bd50d8dfc75a784da246b703b)
      - 80th Birthday Video, 1995 (Box 33, Folder data_value_missing_eef667548930dabcca423e9128cb439a)
        - VHS, 1995; 2010:057:001
          Separated Materials
          Special format items have been separated from the above listed file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - Biographical Sketches (Box 33)
      - Board of Governors of The Nature Conservancy Governor Emeritus Award (Box 33)
      - List of "Letters Book" recipients per David Rockefeller's request after Peggy Rockefeller's death (Box 33)
      - Memorial: "Letters Book", Materials, 1996 (Box 33)
      - Memorial Service Invitation List, 1996 (Box 33)
      - Memorial Service, Obituary and Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 33)
      - The Pillar of New York Award Sept. (Preservation League), 1985 (Box 33)
      - Press Clippings, 1976-1993 (Box 33)
      - Various Stationery Plates and Cards (Box 33)
      - Engagement Books, 1967-1994 (Box 34)
    - Carriage Drives, 1981-1995; 2
      - 1981 May 9 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 1983 May 20-22 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 1983 October 16 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Vermont, 1984 September 13-17 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Williamsburg, Virginia, 1986 October 30 - November 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Brandywine Driving Weekend, 1987 May 1-3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Maine, 1988 October 7-10 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Pocantico Hills, 1991 June 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Maine, 1992 September 29 - October 7 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Columbia County Coaching Society, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Pocantico Hills, 1993 June 7 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Maine, 1993 September 24-30 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Pocantico Hills, 1994 June 6 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - The American Driving Society, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - 1995 February 16 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Carriage Correspondence, 1972-1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Trips, 1986-1996; 3
      - General Travel Information and Brochures (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Vacation Ideas (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Spain and London - The Trilateral Commission, 1986 May 17-24 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Ecuador, 1986 February 5-12 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Spain CMB/IAC, 1987 March 1-4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Thailand and Australia, 1987 November 6-26 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - JY Trip, 1988 July 6-9 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Brazil - Americas Society, 1988 November 5-12 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Poland and Hungary - Council on Foreign Relations, 1989 February 28 - March 8 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Paris, 1989 April 8-10 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Turkey, 1989 June 22-July 4 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Mexico - Americas Society, 1990 February 20-25 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Arizona, 1990 April 5-12 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Ireland, 1990 June 19-July 2 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Sweden, Prague, Vienna, 1991 February 13-24 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Chile, 1991 March 15-27 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Death Valley, 1991 April 1-6 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Alaska, 1991 June 14-22 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Bangkok, 1992 January 31 - February 7 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Mexico, 1995 December 28 - 1996 January 2 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Morocco, 1992 February 8-15 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Chile, 1992 March 13-21 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Alaska - Sail Alaska Reunion, 1992 April 11-12 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Williamsburg, 1992 May 14-16 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Chadd's Ford, Penn. - Brandywine Conservancy, 1992 June 5-6 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - London, 1992 June 12-17 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Puget Sound - San Juan Sailing, 1992 September 6-12 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Baja, California, 1993 January 26-29 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Canada, 1993 June 16-19 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Alaska, Prince William Sound, 1993 July 18-25 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Mexico City, 1993 November 5-10 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - San Francisco, 1994 February 10-13 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - La Paz, 1994 February 27 - March 6 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Erie Canal, 1994 June 20-26 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Scotland, 1994 August 25 - September 6 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - San Francisco, 1994 September 10-11 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Holland, 1995 April 14-24 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Montana - Bar B Guest Ranch, 1995 July 8-18 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Williamsburg, 1995 October 12-16 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Parties, 1949-1996; 4
      - Christmas Parties, Lists, and Gifts, 1992-1996 (Box 38)
      - Christmas Parties, Lists, and Gifts, 1985-1991 (Box 39)
      - Christmas Parties, Lists, and Gifts, 1946-1984 (Box 40)
      - Michael and Barbara Polemis Reception, 1995 October 25 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Farm Party, 1995 January 24 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Harvest Moon Party, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Harvest Party, 1994 December 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Farm Party, 1994 July 2-4 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Farm Party, 1993 July 10 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Cocktail Party Seal Harbor, 1992 August 12 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Farm Party, 1992 July 4 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - House Warming Party - Four Winds, 1990 September 30 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Cocktail Party - Maine, 1988 August 22 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Maine Parties, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Staff Party - Tarrytown, 1986 July 13 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Cocktail Parties - Maine: Seal Harbor, Noreast Harbor, 1983 August 26-31 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Dinner Dance, 1982 October 1 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Casals Concert, 1960 October 11 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - International Dinner, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Van Cliburn and Leonard Bernstein Concert and Dinner, 1958 October 18 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Thursday Evening Club Party, 1958 December 19 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Concert - Bagarotti, 1957 December 17 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Dinner and Concert, 1956 December 29 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Party for Helene Edgell and George Rankling, 1950 June 23 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Dinner/Dance, 1949 June 24 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Gardening and the New York Botanical Garden (NYBG), 1960-1995; 5
      - The Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden (AARG) History and Correspondence, 1962-1992 (Box 42)
      - The Garden Conservancy Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - The Garden Club of America, 1984-1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Gardening Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - NYBG "Beth's Maze" Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - NYBG "Peggy Rockefeller Rose Garden" Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - NYBG Correspondence, 1980-1994 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - NYBG Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - NYBG "A National Historic Landmark" (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - NYBG Proposal to "The Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust for the Development of The Mary Flagler Cary Arboretum" (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - NYBG Materials for the Wild Flowers of the United States Books (Box 44)
      - NYBG Wild Flower Books Donations, 1960-1964 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - NYBG Wild Flower Books Donations, 1965-1967 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - NYBG Lady Bird Johnson Correspondence on the Wild Flowers Books, 1969 April-June (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Book Texas Vol. 3 Books Correspondence - Texas, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Book Texas Vol. 3 Correspondence, Fund Raising Budget, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Book Texas Vol. 3 Clippings, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - NYBG Proposed Forward for Wild Flowers Book Texas Vol. 3; second printing, Undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - NYBG Committee for Wild Flowers Book Texas Vol. 3, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Books Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Books Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Books Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Project Budgets, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - NYBG Wild Flowers Books Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Art, Music, and Cattle, 1959-1995; 6
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - The National Gallery of Art, 1989-1993 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Portland Museum of Art, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - American International Fund, Inc., 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Cantata Singers, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Fundacion Isaac Albeniz, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Julliard School of music, 1974-1987 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Marlboro Music Festival, 1962-1994 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Music Assistance Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - New York Philharmonic, 1959-1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Tanglewood Music Center, 1986-1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Cattle Correspondence and Awards, 1976-1995 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - University of Pennsylvania and Rockefeller University, 1963-1994; 7
      - Board of Trustees Bulletins, 1979-1983 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - School of Veterinary Medicine, 1988-1994 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - School of Veterinary Medicine, 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - School of Veterinary Medicine, 1978-1981 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Agriculture Department of Dairy and Animal Science, 1979-1987 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Docor of Laws Honorary Degree, 1984 October 15 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Second Century Fund: Agriculture Committee, 1984 April 16 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Second Century Fund: Agriculture Committee Meeting, 1983 December 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller University, 1963-1987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Conservation and Preservation, 1973-1996; 8
      - Alexander Calder conservation Award (Conservation Fund), 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - American Bicentennial, 1988 December (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Colonial Williamsburg (Carriage and Stable Complex), 1986-1996 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Columbia Land Conservancy, 1989-1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Conservation Fund, 1984-1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Conservation International, 1987-1992 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Conservation Law Foundation of New England, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Conservation Miscellaneous, 1979-1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Environmental Defense Fund, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Historic Hudson Valley, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1989-1993 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - National Audubon Society, 1976-1994 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - National Conservancy, 1973-1995 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, New York/Washington DC, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - New York Farm Bureau, 1988-1993 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Piedmont Environmental Council, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Tongass National Forest, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Maine, 1963-1995; 9
      - "A History of Bartlett's Island, Mount Desert, Maine" by Esther Binnewies and Muriel Davisson, Drafts, Correspondence, and Related Materials, 1973-1995 (Box 49)
      - Acadia National Park, 1975-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Apprentice Shop, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Buckle Island Correspondence, 1963-1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Business Development in Maine (Miscellaneous), 1965-1978 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - The Chewonki Foundation, 1984-1995 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - College of the Atlantic, 1972-1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Garden Club of Mount Desert, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Governor's Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Island Institute, 1972-1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Maine Department of Environmental Protection, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - The Marine Center, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Natural Resources Council of Maine, 1973-1991 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Outward Bound, 1973-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - General Files, 1965-1996; 10
      - Blue Books - Summary of Contributions, 1965-1996 (Box 51)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1992-1995 (Box 52)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1984-1990 (Box 53)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1976-1982 (Box 54)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1974-1975 (Box 55)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1970-1973 (Box 56)
      - Receipts, Acknowledgements and Contributions, 1966-1969 (Box 57)
      - American Farmland Trust (AFT), 1981-1998 (Box 58)
      - American Farmland Trust (AFT), 1989-1992 (Box 59)
      - American Farmland Trust (AFT), 1993-1996 (Box 60)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT), 1970-1996; 11
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1990-1996 (Box 61)
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1987-1989 (Box 62)
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1980-1986 (Box 63)
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1977-1980 (Box 64)
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1973-1976 (Box 65)
      - Correspondence, Reports, and Campaigns, 1970-1972 (Box 66)
- Accession 2011:004, 1936-1945; 2; 2.64 Cubic Feet 6 standard document storage boxes
  - Personal Files, 1942-1943; 3
    - Blueprint, Undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Pelleas and Melisande, Lyric Drama in Five Acts (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Pets ("Kit"), 1942 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Rent, 1943 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - War Department Benefits (David), 1943 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1945; 4
    - (Aunt) Lucy Aldrich, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - "A" Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Clara Berman, Undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - "B" Miscellaneous, 1940-1946 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Pierre Chenye, 1943-1945 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Dick Crenshaw, Undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - "C" Miscellaneous, 1940-1945 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - A. F. (Fair) Dana, 1943 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - R. H. Dana, 1943-1945 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - "D" Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Mrs. George Franklin (Georgie), 1944 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - "F" Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Anne and Richard Gilder, 1942-1945 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Heribert, 1936-1938 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - "H/I/J" Miscellaneous, 1940-1943 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - "L" Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Abby Rockefeller Mauze, Undated (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Eileen McGrath, 1942-1945 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Hinnie McGrath, 1941-1944 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Gordon McGrath, 1942-1945 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. Neva McGrath, 1938-1940 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Sims McGrath, 1940-1945 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Sims McGrath (from Peggy Rockefeller), 1945 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Mac and Margaret Millard, 1944 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - "M/N" Miscellaneous, 1940-1944 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Nancy, 1936-1938 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Captain J. B. Oakes, 1943-1944 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Alice Otis, Undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - "P" Miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "Q" Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1940 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Blanchette Rockefeller, 1940 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - David Rockefeller, 1938-1940 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - David Rockefeller, 1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - David Rockefeller, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - David Rockefeller, 1945 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - David Rockefeller (from Peggy Rockefeller), 1944 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1941-1945 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Nelson Rockefeller, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Peggy Rockefeller (Carbons), 1941-1944 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - "R" Miscellaneous, 1940-1945 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Lieutenant De Veaux Smith, Undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - "S" Miscellaneous, 1941-1943 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - "T" Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Correspondence (1), 1937-1945 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Correspondence (2), 1937-1945 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified, 1940-1945 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Universitats - Augenkunik Munchen, 1936 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - "V" Miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Lt. F. Peter Weil, 1941-1945 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Western Union, 1941-1945 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - "W" Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Bank and Engagement Books, 1940-1944; 5
    - Family Engagement Pads, 1941-1944 (Box 70)
    - Bank Book, 1940 September 9 - 1941 February 7 (Box 70)
    - Bank Book, 1941 February 10 - July 14 (Box 70)
    - Bank Book, 1941 July 21 - October 1 (Box 70)
    - Bank Book, 1942 May 12 - October 9 (Box 70)
    - Bank Book, 1942 November 2 - 1943 March 19 (Box 70)
    - Miscellaneous photo (Box 70)
  - Photographs and Negatives, 6
    - Bartlett's Island (Box 70)
    - Home Construction (Box 71)
    - David Rockefeller (Box 71)
    - Pocantico (Box 71)
    - Margaret Rockefeller and Children (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 71)
    - Unlabeled envelopes of negatives (Box 72)
- Accession 2003:106 - Apartment Files, 3
  - Personal Files, 1966-1984; 7
    - Acknowledgement Letters, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Acknowledgement Letters, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Bank and Engagement Books, 1975-1978 (Box 73, Item 1-8)
    - Christmas, 1974-1979 (Box 74)
    - Christmas, 1980 (Box 75)
    - Contributions, 1976-1984 (Box 76)
    - Construction and Land Agreements, 1983-1984 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Decorating, 1973-1975 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Decorating, 1975-1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Decorating Receipts, 1966-1971 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Decorating - Stone House Farm, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Richard Rockefeller Materials, 1967-1971 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Flower file (Bill Swihura), 1970-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Flower and Vegetable Orders, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Flowers, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Flowers, 1976-1980 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Flowers - Seal Harbor, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Flowers and Seeds, 1980-1982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Flowers Miscellaneous, 1970-1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Get Well Soon Cards, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Jewelry, 1967-1979 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Medical Files, 1973-1980 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      Restricted from scholarly access - confidential material.
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Parties, 1971-1976 (Box 79)
    - Passport, 1982-1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files, 1975-1977 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files, 1975-1984 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      Restricted from scholarly access - personnel material.
    - Security, 1970-1983 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Subscriptions and Associations, 1974-1980 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Warranties and Receipts, 1973-1976 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Wedding, Undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1984; 8
    - A-C (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
    - Connolly, Sybil, 1980-1983 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - D-F (Box 81, Folder 5-7)
    - Form Letters, 1975-1978 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - G-K (Box 82, Folder 1-5)
    - Kaiser, Neva and Walter, 1968-1980 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - L-P (Box 82, Folder 7-11)
    - R-S (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - Scott, Leslie - Hudson Pines, 1972-1973 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Leslie - Pocantico Farms, 1972-1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - T-Y (Box 83, Folder 5-8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1983 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3-4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
    - Carbon Copies, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Carbon Copies, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 8-9)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT), 1972-1984; 9
    - General Files, 1972-1983; 1
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1972-1982 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Budget Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, 1972-1975 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Staff Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising Materials, 1972-1984; 2
      - 1972-1975 (Box 86)
      - 1976-1983 (Box 87)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 88)
    - Acknowledgement Letters, 1980-1983; 3
      - A - General, 1980-1983 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Aldrich, Hope, 1980-1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Astor, Vincent and Brooke, 1980-1982 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - B - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Bernhard, Robert, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Berwind, Graham Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Black, Peter, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Blum, Robert, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - C - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Camp, Frederic E., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Chatfield, Albert and Marian, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Cox, Thomas, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Dayton, Alida, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Dillon, Douglas, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - E - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Engelhard, Charles and Jane, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - F - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - H - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Hartwell, Davis, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Hopkins, Luke and Kitty, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Huber, Hans A., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - I - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - Ingalls, Mabel S., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - Jennings, Brewster and Kate, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - K - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 25)